Guide to the Democratic Socialists of America Records TAM.105
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series X. Membership and Fundraising, 1971-2015; 3.94 Linear Feet in 9 manuscript boxes; 2.19 Megabytes in 161 computer files
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) and Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- Key List Mailings, 1982 (Box 244, Folder 3-4)
  - Key List Mailings, 1983 (Box 244, Folder 5, Box 245, Folder 1)
  - Key List Mailings, 1984 (Box 245, Folder 2-3)
  - Key List Mailings, 1985 (Box 245, Folder 4)
  - Key List Mailings, 1986 (Box 246, Folder 1-2)
  - Key List Mailings, 1987 (Box 246, Folder 3-4)
  - Key List Mailings, 1988-1990 (Box 246, Folder 5)
  - Key List Mailings, 1992 (Box 246, Folder 6)
  - Key List Mailings, 1993 (Box 247, Folder 1-2)
  - Key List Mailings, 1994 (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Key List Mailings, 1995 (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - Key List Mailings, 1996-1997
    - Paper Files (Box 247, Folder 5)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_190
  - Key List Mailing, 1999; TW_TAM_105_ER_188
  - Key List Mailing, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 6)
  - Key List Mailing, 2002; TW_TAM_105_ER_189
  - Deb's Club Newsletter, 2014-2016 (Box 343, Folder 12)
  - Fundraising and Grants, 1972-1978 (Box 247, Folder 7)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Fundraising, 1972-1981 (Box 334, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising and Grants, 1979-1981 (Box 248, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising and Grants, 1982-1988 (Box 248, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising and Grants, 1989-1991 (Box 248, Folder 3)
  - Fundraising and Grants, 1992-1993 (Box 248, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising and Grants, 1994-1997
    - Paper Files (Box 248, Folder 5)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_186
  - Fundraising and Grants, 1998-2004; TW_TAM_105_ER_187
- Series XI. Socialist International, 1951-2006; 3.51 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes and 1 oversized flat file folder; 150 kilobytes in 6 computer files
  This series illustrates DSA's international reach, as the sole U.S. affiliate of Socialist International after 2005 until it left in 2017. It contains printed matter (bulletins and press releases) from Socialist International and other international organizations; conference materials; meeting minutes; and correspondence.
  - Publications by Socialist International and Other Countries, 1951-1972 (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and International Publications, 1973 (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and International Publications, 1974 (Box 249, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence and International Publications, 1975 (Box 249, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, International Publications, and Socialist International Congress Meeting Notes, 1976 (Box 249, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Circulars, and International Publications, 1977 (Box 249, Folder 6, Box 250, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Circulars, and International Publications, 1978 (Box 250, Folder 2-3)
  - Correspondence, Circulars, and International Publications, 1979 (Box 251, Folder 1-3)
  - Correspondence, Conference Materials, and International Publications, 1980 (Box 252, Folder 1-3, Box 253, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence, Conference Proceedings, and International Publications, 1981 (Box 253, Folder 3, Box 254, Folder 1-2, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Conference Materials, and International Publications, 1982 (Box 254, Folder 3-4)
  - Correspondence, Conference Proceedings, and International Publications, 1983 (Box 255, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence, Circulars, Meeting Minutes, and International Publications, 1984-1986 (Box 255, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Circulars, and Statements, 1988-1989 (Box 255, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Proposals, Resolutions, and Circulars, 1990 (Box 255, Folder 5, Box 256, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Meeting Resolutions and Declarations, and Newsletter, 1991-1993 (Box 256, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Meeting Resolutions, and Working Paper, 1995-1999
    - Paper Files (Box 256, Folder 3)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_194
  - Council Resolutions and Statements, 2001
    - Paper Files (Box 256, Folder 4)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_195
  - Council Resolutions, Statements, and Meeting Materials, 2002-2003
    - Paper Files (Box 256, Folder 5)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_196
  - Council Resolutions and Address Lists, 2004-2006 (Box 256, Folder 6)
  - Socialist Affairs and Socialist International Women Bulletin -- Incomplete, 1979-1997 (Box 256, Folder 7)
- Series XII. Institute for Democratic Socialism/Democratic Socialists of America Fund, 1978-1991; 1.81 Linear Feet in 3 manuscript boxes and 2 flat boxes; 43 audiocassettes; 33.5 kilobytes in 1 document
  Arranged chronologically generally.
  This series contains materials related to the Institute for Democratic Socialism (IDS), which was founded in 1978 to help spread democratic socialist ideals through educational materials and activist training. In the mid-1990s, IDS changed its name to the Democratic Socialists of America Fund. Materials consist of conference proposals and programs, correspondence, fundraising materials, and membership records. Materials also include audio recordings of speeches and panels from the "Eurosocialism and America" conference, a three-day conference in 1980, in which U.S. activists met with international leaders of social democratic and democratic socialist political movements to explore how democratic socialist policy alternatives could benefit the U.S. Notable individuals featured in the recordings include world leaders like Willy Brandt (Germany), Olof Palme (Sweden), Joop den Uyl (Netherlands), Francois Mitterand (France), as well as Michael Harrington, union leader William Winpisinger, Representative Ron Dellums, and Gloria Steinem.
  - Jamaica Study Group Tour and Meeting with Prime Minister Michael Manley, 1978 (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - Conference -- "Eurosocialism and America: An International Exchange", December 5-7, 1980
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Flyers, December 5-7, 1980 (Box 257, Folder 2-4, Box 258, Folder 1-2)
    - "Democratizing Our Societies", December 5-7, 1980
      - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0041)
      - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0042)
    - "A Responsible Party System", December 5-7, 1980
      - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0043)
      - Audio Recording (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0273)
    - "Right Wing Attacks on the Left", December 5-7, 1980 (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0044)
    - "Democratizing Capital Formation", December 5-7, 1980
      - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0045)
      - Audio Recording (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0286)
    - "Controlling Inflation", December 5-7, 1980 (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0046)
    - "Trends in the Tax System", December 5-7, 1980
      - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0047)
      - Audio Recording (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0280)
    - "Industrial Dislocation", December 5-7, 1980
      - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0048)
      - Audio Recording (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0278)
    - "Multinational Corporations", December 5-7, 1980 (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0049)
    - "Economic Stagnation", December 5-7, 1980 (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0050)
    - "Unions and Politics", December 5-7, 1980 (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0051)
    - "Workers in Management", December 5-7, 1980
      - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0052)
      - Audio Recording (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0285)
    - "Combatting Discrimination", December 5-7, 1980
      - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0053)
      - Audio Recording (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0277)
    - "Quality of Life", December 5-7, 1980 (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0054)
    - "Universal Health Care Systems", December 5-7, 1980
      - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0055)
      - Audio Recording (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0276)
    - "Why No Mass Socialist Movement?", December 5-7, 1980
      - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0056)
      - Audio Recording (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0271)
    - "Adjusting to Aging Population", December 5-7, 1980
      - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0057)
      - Audio Recording (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0275)
    - "Housing", December 5-7, 1980 (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0058)
    - "Democratizing/Political Process", December 5-7, 1980
      - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0059)
      - Audio Recording (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0274)
    - "Participation/Political Process", December 5-7, 1980 (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0060)
    - "A Program for Survival", December 5-7, 1980 (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0061)
    - "Control and Content/Popular Media", December 5-7, 1980
      - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0062)
      - Audio Recording (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0270)
    - "The Challenge of Education", December 5-7, 1980 (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0063)
    - "Unions and Politics", December 5-7, 1980 (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0268)
    - "Right Wing Attacks on the Left", December 5-7, 1980 (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0269)
    - "Cultural Hegemony: Whose?", December 5-7, 1980 (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0272)
    - "Maintaining Full Employment", December 5-7, 1980 (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0279)
    - "Responses to Economic Stagnation", December 5-7, 1980 (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0281)
    - Opening Plenary Session, December 5-7, 1980
      - Audio Recording (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0283)
      - Audio Recording (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0284)
    - "Democratizing/Social Structure", December 5-7, 1980
      - Audio Recording (Box 154, Audiocassette 105.0040)
      - Audio Recording (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0282)
  - Democracy in the Americas Project, 1981-1982 (Box 258, Folder 3-4)
  - Convention -- "Deadly Connections: Latin American Intervention, Nuclear Escalation, and the Economic Crisis -- The Socialist Response", October 1984 (Box 258, Folder 5)
  - Conference -- "The War at Home: Organizing for Economic and Social Justice", 2003; TW_TAM_105_ER_197
  - Governance -- Board Minutes, Correspondence, and Bylaws, 1979-1991 (Box 259, Folder 1)
  - Membership -- Key List and New Member Mailings, 1979-1990 (Box 259, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 259, Folder 3)
  - Grants Received, 1981-1993 (Box 259, Folder 4)
  - Proposals for Possibly Unrealized Projects, 1981-1984 (Box 259, Folder 5)
- Series XIII. Subject Files, 1906-2008; 18.17 Linear Feet in 40 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, and 1 folder in 1 shared box; 7 VHS; 1 Sound_Disc--Vinyl; 3.55 Gigabytes in 60 computer files
  This series includes printed matter (newsletters, brochures, bulletins, conference materials, and journals) from organizations with which DSA and its predecessor organizations worked and supported, such as the Democratic National Committee, Democratic Party, United Farm Workers of America, and American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO). Also covered are topics of interest to DSA and its members, such as pro-democracy movements, civil rights, international solidarity, and Puerto Rican independence. These materials mostly include clippings and articles but there are a few documentaries as well. "Incomplete" indicates that there is not a complete run of issues for a particular publication.
  - Adams, Richard W. -- "Citizens", circa 1989 (Box 161, Vhs 105.0190)
  - Affirmative Action, 2001; TW_TAM_105_ER_198
  - Affirmative Action Coordinating Center, 1978-1979 (Box 260, Folder 1)
  - Africa, 1974-1992 (Box 260, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture and Food, 1970-1985 (Box 260, Folder 3, Box 335, Folder 1)
  - Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU), 1975-1989 (Box 260, Folder 4)
  - "Am I Blue? A Report on the Threat to Excellence at Yale", undated (Box 161, Vhs 105.0191)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1971-1997 (Box 260, Folder 5-7)
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1978-1980 (Box 261, Folder 1, Box 335, Folder 2)
  - American Friends Service Committee (AFSC), 1977-1979 (Box 335, Folder 3)
  - The American Jewish Committee, 1974-1979 (Box 261, Folder 2)
  - American Political State, 1975-1980 (Box 261, Folder 3)
  - American Political State, 1995-2003; TW_TAM_105_ER_199
  - Americans for Democratic Action (ADA), 1973-1989 (Box 261, Folder 4-5)
  - Amnesty International, 1973-1983 (Box 261, Folder 6)
  - Anti-Draft Movement, 1978-1982 (Box 261, Folder 7)
  - Anti-Poverty Programs, 1979-1996 (Box 261, Folder 8)
  - Anti-Racism -- Organizations, Programs, and Publications, 1971-1994 (Box 261, Folder 9, Box 262, Folder 1-2, Box 335, Folder 4)
  - Appalachian Alliance, 1978 (Box 335, Folder 5)
  - Arms Race and Disarmament, 1972-1992 (Box 262, Folder 3-4)
  - Association for Union Democracy, circa 1970-1986 (Box 263, Folder 1)
  - Association of Community Organizations for Reform Now (ACORN), 1975-1980 (Box 263, Folder 2, Box 335, Folder 6)
  - Attica Brigade, circa 1972-1974 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - The Baron Report -- Incomplete, 1979-1980 (Box 263, Folder 4)
  - Black Liberation Movement, 1973-1986 (Box 263, Folder 5)
  - Black Panther Party, 1976-1991 (Box 263, Folder 6-7)
  - Black People -- Politics and Government, 1976-1986 (Box 263, Folder 8)
  - Black Political Prisoners, 1973-1995 (Box 263, Folder 9)
  - Blazing Star -- Incomplete, 1978-1979 (Box 263, Folder 10)
  - Breira, 1973-1977 (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - Bureau of National Affairs, 1972 (Box 335, Folder 7)
  - Campaign to Stop Government Spying/Campaign for Political Rights, 1977-1979 (Box 264, Folder 2, Box 335, Folder 8)
  - The Catholic Worker -- Incomplete, 1979-1985 (Box 264, Folder 3)
  - Center for Campus Organizing, 1995-1996 (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - Center of Concern, 1975-1979 (Box 264, Folder 5, Box 335, Folder 9)
  - Central America, Mexico, and the Caribbean, 1973-1995 (Box 264, Folder 6-7, Box 265, Folder 1, Box 335, Folder 10)
  - Challenge, 1938-1939 (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - Chile, 1974-1979 (Box 265, Folder 3, Box 335, Folder 11)
  - Citizen Action Groups, 1979-1999 (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Review Commission on the FBI, 1977 (Box 265, Folder 5)
  - Civil and Human Rights, 1962-1999
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_200
    - Paper Files (Box 265, Folder 6, Box 266, Folder 1-2, Box 335, Folder 12)
  - Clinton Administration, 1992 (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - Cloward, Richard A. -- Denial of Reappointment at Brandeis University, 1979 (Box 266, Folder 4)
  - Coalition for a Democratic Majority, 1974-1984 (Box 266, Folder 5)
  - Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Rights, 1985-1986 (Box 266, Folder 6)
  - Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy, 1976-1979 (Box 335, Folder 13)
  - Coalition for a People's Alternative in 1980 (Box 266, Folder 7)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, 1972-1979 (Box 266, Folder 8)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1974-1988 (Box 266, Folder 9, Box 335, Folder 14)
  - Committee for Artistic and Intellectual Freedom in Iran, 1974-1977 (Box 267, Folder 1)
  - Committee for Public Justice, 1977-1979 (Box 267, Folder 2)
  - Committee for Socialist Education, 1974-1976 (Box 267, Folder 3)
  - Committee for the Suit Against Government Misconduct, 1973-1981 (Box 267, Folder 4)
  - Committee to Save the Iranian 14, 1979 (Box 267, Folder 5)
  - Committees of Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 267, Folder 6)
  - Communism, 1967-1992 (Box 267, Folder 7)
  - Community Ownership Organizing Project, 1977 (Box 335, Folder 15)
  - Conference on Alternative State and Local Policies, 1976-1984 (Box 267, Folder 8-9, Box 335, Folder 16)
  - Congress of Afrikan People, 1974-1975 (Box 336, Folder 1)
  - Consumer Federation of America, undated (Box 336, Folder 2)
  - Corporations, 1973-1995 (Box 267, Folder 10, Box 268, Folder 1)
  - Council on Hemispheric Affairs, 1977-1984 (Box 268, Folder 2)
  - Cover Up: Behind the Iran Contra Affair, 1988 (Box 162, Vhs 105.0199)
  - D. C. Statehood Party, 1972 (Box 268, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Candidates and Elected Officials, 1972-1995 (Box 268, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Leadership Council, 1985-1986, 1997
    - Paper Files (Box 268, Folder 5)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_201
  - Democratic National Committee, 1968-1986 (Box 268, Folder 6)
  - Democratic Planning Group, 1973-1975 (Box 268, Folder 7)
  - Democratic Policy Commission, 1985-1986 (Box 269, Folder 1)
  - "A la Deriva por los Circuitos de la Precariedad Femenina", 2003; TW_TAM_105_ER_220
  - Detroit Alliance for a Rational Economy (DARE), 1978 (Box 336, Folder 3)
  - The Developing Country Courier, June-October 1979 (Box 269, Folder 2)
  - Economic Issues
    - Paper Files, 1968-1998 (Box 269, Folder 3-4, Box 336, Folder 4)
    - Electronic Files, 2003; TW_TAM_105_ER_202
  - Education, 1972-1995 (Box 269, Folder 5, Box 336)
  - El Salvador, 1980-1991 (Box 269, Folder 6)
  - Energy Alternatives, 1972-1981 (Box 270, Folder 1-4)
  - Environment, 1973-2004 (Box 270, Folder 5, Box 336, Folder 6)
  - Environmentalists for Full Employment, 1976-1978 (Box 336, Folder 7)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1975 (Box 336, Folder 8)
  - Eritrea, 1975-1988 (Box 271, Folder 1)
  - Eugene V. Debs Foundation, 1964-1975 (Box 271, Folder 2)
  - Fair Share, 1977 (Box 336, Folder 9)
  - Families of Resisters for Amnesty (FORA), 1973 (Box 336, Folder 10)
  - Feminism, 1975-1978 (Box 271, Folder 3)
  - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Records on New American Movement (NAM), 1971-1975 (Box 271, Folder 4-8, Box 272, Folder 1-6, Box 273, Folder 1)
  - Freedom Socialist Party, 1969, 1985-1986 (Box 273, Folder 2, Box 336, Folder 11)
  - Friends of the Earth, 1977-1979 (Box 273, Folder 3)
  - Full Employment, 1975-1992 (Box 273, Folder 4)
  - "Future Watch", undated (Box 162, Vhs 105.0198)
  - Global Affairs, 1979-2002
    - Paper Files (Box 273, Folder 5)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_203
  - Global Economy, 1979-2004
    - Paper Files (Box 273, Folder 6)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_204
  - hooks, bell, 1989-1992 (Box 273, Folder 7)
  - Health and Health Care, 1975-1997
    - Paper Files (Box 273, Folder 8)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_205
  - Highlander Research and Education Center, 1978 (Box 336, Folder 12)
  - Housing, 1978-1998 (Box 273, Folder 9)
  - Illinois Public Action Council, 1976 (Box 336, Folder 13)
  - Immigration Reform
    - Conference Program, 1978 (Box 336, Folder 14)
    - Electronic Records, 2003; TW_TAM_105_ER_206
  - Imperialism, 1967-1983 (Box 273, Folder 10, Box 336, Folder 15)
  - Indian Opinion, 1975-1976 (Box 273, Folder 11)
  - Indigenous Peoples -- North America, 1973-1992 (Box 273, Folder 12)
  - Institute for Local Self-Reliance, 1978 (Box 336, Folder 16)
  - The Institute on the Church in Urban-Industrial Society (ICUIS), 1974-1977 (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - Intercommunal Survival Committee, 1975 (Box 336, Folder 17)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM), 1978-1981 (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Traders, 1970-1972 (Box 274, Folder 3)
  - International Labor Movements and Publications, 1974-1983 (Box 274, Folder 4)
  - International Socialist Parties and Publications, 1973-1989, 2001
    - Paper Files (Box 274, Folder 5, Box 336, Folder 18)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_207
  - Iranian Students Association, 1976 (Box 336, Folder 19)
  - Ireland, 1971-1986 (Box 274, Folder 6)
  - Israel, 1975-2002
    - Paper Files (Box 274, Folder 7)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_208
  - Italy and US, May 1979 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Socialist Youth Bund, 1975-1976 (Box 274, Folder 9)
  - Jobs and Justice, 1978-1979 (Box 274, Folder 10)
  - John Brown Anti-Klan Committee, 1977-1987 (Box 274, Folder 11)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies, 1973-1977 (Box 336, Folder 20)
  - Joint Economic Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 274, Folder 12, Box 275, Folder 1)
  - Journal of Current Social Issues, Spring 1974 (Box 275, Folder 2)
  - Journal of World Education, 1973 (Box 336, Folder 21)
  - Kahn, Kathy and Danny McMahan -- "Coors Brewery Strike Songs", 1977 (Box Shared Tamiment 176, Sound disc--vinyl 105.0218)
  - Labor and Other Documentary Films, 1964-1987 (Box 276, Folder 2, Box 336, Folder 22)
  - Labor and Workers, 1945-1973 (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - Labor and Workers, 1968-1980 (Box 337, Folder 1)
  - Labor and Workers, 1974-1978 (Box 275, Folder 4)
  - Labor and Workers, 1978-1979 (Box 275, Folder 5)
  - Labor and Workers, 1980-1988 (Box 275, Folder 6)
  - Labor and Workers, 1988-2008 (Box 276, Folder 1)
  - League for Industrial Democracy, 1969-1978 (Box 276, Folder 3)
  - League for Proletarian Socialism, 1976 (Box 337, Folder 2)
  - The "Left", 1972-2001 (Box 276, Folder 4)
  - Legislation, 1975-1984 (Box 276, Folder 5-6)
  - The Lesbian Feminist, August 1973 (Box 276, Folder 7)
  - Local Progressive Newsletters, 1965-1995 (Box 276, Folder 8, Box 337, Folder 3)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Center for Social Change, 1972-1979 (Box 276, Folder 9)
  - Mass Party Organizing Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - Mass Transit, 1975-1985 (Box 277, Folder 1)
  - May 19th Communist Organization, 1977-1982 (Box 277, Folder 2)
  - Marx, Karl, 1990 (Box 277, Folder 3)
  - Media, circa 1971-1995 (Box 277, Folder 4, Box 337, Folder 5)
  - Medical Committee for Human Rights, 1971-1972 (Box 337, Folder 6)
  - The Methodist Federation for Social Action, 1974-1977 (Box 337, Folder 7)
  - The Middle East, 1975-2006
    - Paper Files (Box 277, Folder 5)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_214
  - Midwest Academy, 1972-1976 (Box 337, Folder 8)
  - Military and Foreign Policy -- United States, 1967-2004 (Box 277, Folder 6-7)
  - Minimum Wage, 1984-1996
    - Paper Files (Box 277, Folder 8)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_209
  - Mobilization for Survival, 1976-1979 (Box 337, Folder 9)
  - Moncada Library, 1978-1982 (Box 277, Folder 9)
  - Movement for Economic Justice, 1975-1978 (Box 337, Folder 10)
  - Movement for a New Society, 1975-1977 (Box 338, Folder 1)
  - Music, 1977-1991 (Box 277, Folder 10)
  - National Alliance of Black Feminists, 1978 (Box 338, Folder 2)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1971-1973 (Box 277, Folder 11)
  - National Black Political Assembly, 1975 (Box 338, Folder 3)
  - National Campaign to Impeach Nixon, 1973-1974 (Box 277, Folder 12)
  - National Caucus of Labor Committees, 1973-1974 (Box 277, Folder 13)
  - National Committee Against Repressive Legislation (NCARL), 1976-1978 (Box 338, Folder 4)
  - National Committee to Reopen the Rosenberg Case, 1976 (Box 277, Folder 14)
  - National Democratic Institute for International Affairs, 1988-1989 (Box 278, Folder 1)
  - National Labor Committee, 1995 (Box 278, Folder 2)
  - National Lawyer's Guild, 1971-1979 (Box 278, Folder 3, Box 338, Folder 5)
  - National Legislative Education Foundation, 1986 (Box 278, Folder 4)
  - National Organisation of Labour Student Women's Committee -- Great Britain, 1979 (Box 278, Folder 6)
  - National Organization for Women (NOW), 1979-1995 (Box 278, Folder 5, Box 338, Folder 6)
  - National Peoples Action/National Training and Information Center, 1976-1979 (Box 278, Folder 8, Box 338, Folder 7)
  - National Tenants Organization, 1972-1974 (Box 278, Folder 7)
  - National Urban League, 1976-1984 (Box 278, Folder 9)
  - National Women's Political Caucus, 1980 (Box 278, Folder 10)
  - Native American Solidarity Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 338, Folder 8)
  - Neighborhood Organizations, 1976-1977 (Box 278, Folder 11)
  - New Action Party, 1975-1978 (Box 338, Folder 9)
  - New Democratic Coalition (NDC), 1973-1985 (Box 278, Folder 12)
  - New Democratic Party (NDP) -- Canada, 1977-1979 (Box 279, Folder 1, Box 338, Folder 10)
  - New Party, circa 1990-1993 (Box 279, Folder 2)